CV. Mamolatelo Ronny Pitsi

Full Stack Developer

PERSONAL DETAILS

Last Name: Pitsi

First Name: Mamolatelo (Preferred name: Ronny)

Nationality: South African ID Number: 9112315535082

Phone: 0790613825 / 0678615542 Email: ronnyslow777@gmail.com

Location: Pretoria
Gender: Male
Race: African

Languages: English, Sepedi



EDUCATION & QUALIFICATIONS

Date	Institution/Organisation	Degree/Diploma/Certificate
2015	University of Limpopo	Bachelor of Science Degree: Mathematics and Computer Science
2009	Kgalushi High School	Senior Certificate (Grade 12 / Matric / High School Diploma)

CERTIFICATES/COURSES/TRAINING

Date	Institution/Organisation	Certificate/Course/Training
2011	Seshego FET College	N4 Engineering Studies
2016	Tshwane IDC (VR Innovation Academy)	VR Software Development

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

September 2018 - Present Mobility-online(E-dealerportal)

Web Developer

Overview:

Work collaboratively with design and other specialist teams, client delivery and account management, as well as working directly with the clients where needed. Analyse business requirements and internal design as well as develop system requirements. Develop structured clean reusable code. Focus on the quality and best technical approach to ensure the overall delivery of projects is on time, on budget.

Technologies:

• CSS, JavaScript, HTML, ASP.NET, C#, MySQL, SQL, PHP, jQuery, Json, xml, Html5, Bootstrap, WordPress ☐ Visual Studio Code, Visual Studio, WCF, Web Service, API

Responsibilities/Contributions:

- Design server-side architecture.
- Build the front-end of applications through appealing visual design.
- Develop and manage well-functioning databases and applications.
- Write effective APIs, Test software to ensure responsiveness and efficiency.
- Troubleshoot, debug and upgrade software.
- Build features and applications with a mobile responsive design. ☐ API integration

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

June 2017 - June 2018 (Contract)

Accenture

Intern Java Developer

Technologies:

- SoapUI, API Store (Automation testing), Angular.js, Node.js, Html, CSS, JavaScript, ionic framework, Json
- eclipse, NetBeans, Jenkins, Visual Studio Code, Responsibilities/Contributions:
- Accenture South32 Data Cleansing (Aug 2017 Jun 2018) O Cleanse open PO's that are no longer in use in preparation for Quadrium to Ariba network using SAP.
- Accenture Discovery VHR (Jun 2017 July 2017)

 I was part of a testing team working at Discovery where we had to test applications for the client for their health system, we were using SoapUI and API Store to test this project.
 - O Testing create an account, login, delete and capture all the assessments, can track the point and check progress of the assessment.
 - o integration platform Services. o managed assessments micro services assessments.
 - o Assessment agreement events point service micro service.

Reason for Leaving: Contract successfully completed.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

April 2016 - March 2017 (Contract)

Tshwane Interactive Digital Centre (Through the Innovation Hub)

Trainee Developer

Technologies:

- html, CSS, JavaScript,
- Eon studio, 3d max, Photoshop

Responsibilities/Contributions:

- Engagement in the specialized training program through the Tshwane Interactive digital Centre.
- The development and production of VR/AR content and applications.
- The development of business concepts for targeted VR market applications.

Reason for Leaving: Contract successfully completed.

PART-TIME AD-HOC EXPERIENCE

April 2015 - October 2015 (Contract)

University of Limpopo (Turfloop Campus - School of Mathematics and Computer Science)

Mathematics Assistant - For first year students

Responsibilities/Contributions:

- Assisting students solving mathematics problems during mathematics tutorials.
- Invigilating tests and quizzes.

Reason for Leaving: Contract successfully completed.

TECHNICAL PROFICIENCY

- SoapUI, API Store (Automation testing).
- Angular.js, Node.js, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JavaScript framework Ionic.
- Java, C++, PHP (basics), MySQL (basic).
- Eon studio, 3d Max, Eclipse, NetBeans, Jenkins, Visual Studio Code.
- ASP.NET, C#, SOL